https://www.retirenet.com/article/2-privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - Retirement Net by
The Retirement Net Premier retirement living featuring retirement communities and retirement homes in planned active developments. Worldwide resource for active retirement senior communities, rv/resort homes, vacation homes and assisted living facilities. The Retirement Net is the most comprehensive resource of premier retirement communities throughout the world featuring site built homes, manufactured homes, assisted living facilities, planned active retirement communities and various retirement properties worldwide. See also: senior housing, retirement communities, retirement living, elder care network.
Community Search:
Alabama
South Alabama
Central Alabama
North Alabama
Alaska
Bristol Bay and Aleutian Islands - Alaska
Bush Alaska
Anchorage and Kenai Peninsula - Alaska
Home
»
Articles
»
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Editorial Staff
My Saved Searches
Sign In or Create your free account to see your saved searches.
Search by city, state, zipcode or community
Sign In
Sign Up
Home
Resources
Advertise
MyRetireNet
Add Your Community
A community Showcase on RetireNet.com is the best way to generate the sales leads.
FIND OUT MORE
Become A Team Agent
If
you're a real estate agent, here's how you can start working with RetireNet.com.
FIND OUT MORE
Site Map |
Home |
Experts |
Articles
About Us |
Privacy Policy |
Advertise |
Visit CommunitiesNet |
Visit Retirenet Care |
Send Us Feedback |
Secure Sign-In
Browse Communities By Region
Browse Maps
To view 55+ retirement communities for a state, choose from the list below:
Alabama, Alaska,
Arizona, Arkansas,
California, Colorado,
Connecticut, Delaware,
District of Columbia,
Florida, Georgia,
Hawaii, Idaho,
Illinois, Indiana,
Iowa, Kansas,
Kentucky, Louisiana,
Maine, Maryland,
Massachusetts, Michigan,
Minnesota, Mississippi,
Missouri, Montana,
Nebraska, Nevada,
New Hampshire, New Jersey,
New Mexico, New York,
North Carolina, North Dakota,
Ohio, Oklahoma,
Oregon, Pennsylvania,
Rhode Island, South Carolina,
South Dakota, Tennessee,
Texas, Utah,
Vermont, Virginia,
Washington,
West Virginia, Wisconsin,
Wyoming
To view Assisted Living Facilities, Homes and Communities for a state, choose from the list below:
Alabama, Alaska,
Arizona, Arkansas,
California, Colorado,
Connecticut, Delaware,
District of Columbia,
Florida, Georgia,
Hawaii, Idaho,
Illinois, Indiana,
Iowa, Kansas,
Kentucky, Louisiana,
Maine, Maryland,
Massachusetts, Michigan,
Minnesota, Mississippi,
Missouri, Montana,
Nebraska, Nevada,
New Hampshire, New Jersey,
New Mexico, New York,
North Carolina, North Dakota,
Ohio, Oklahoma,
Oregon, Pennsylvania,
Rhode Island, South Carolina,
South Dakota, Tennessee,
Texas, Utah,
Vermont, Virginia,
Washington,
West Virginia, Wisconsin,
Wyoming
To view retirement communities for a province or territory, choose from the list below:
Alberta, British Columbia,
Manitoba, New Brunswick,
Newfoundland and Labrador, Northwest Territories,
Nova Scotia, Nunavut,
Ontario, Prince Edward Island,
Quebec, Saskatchewan,
Yukon Territory
Home
Resources
Advertise
MyRetireNet
Welcome, Guest!   Sign InSign Up
Home
Resources
Advertise
MyRetireNet
Sign In
Sign Up
Obtain Account Activation Email x
Enter the e-mail address you registered with below. Within one minute you will receive an email with instructions on completing the setup for your account.
Send
Password Reset Verify your Identity x
In order to reset your password, we need to verify your identity. Enter your email address below and we will email you a link to reset your password. If you don't know your email address or you can't receive email at that address, contact support.
Send
You have successfully registered with Retirenet!
x
The last step required to complete the signup process is to verify your registration by clicking the link found in the email sent to you. Let's Get Started
Take me to my dashboard
Stay here
Secure Sign-In x
Important: If you have not previously signed up as user, Click here as the first step to set up your account.
If you have registered but have lost or not received your confirmation email, click here.
Remember me on this computer
Sign InForgot your password?
Terms of Service | Privacy Policy | Not registered yet?
Date of birth:
Fill out the following form to send a friend information about this item.
Your form has been submitted.
Please enter your screen name or email address and password. Not a member?
Sign up!
Sign up for a free account so you can save searches and track your favorite communities.
It only takes a minute!
IMPORTANT: In order to create your account, you must be able to receive a confirmation
email from RetireNet.com. If you are using a spam filter with your email program, please make sure
that you retirenet.com is in your list of approved domains.
Already have an account?
Sign in!
Verify your Identity
In order to reset your password, we need to verify your identity. Enter your email address below and we
will email you a link to reset your password. If you don't know your email address or you can't receive email at
that address, contact support.
Email
Continue
Return to Sign-in
